poop
"Your all short. You should rob a dragon."
no one agrees
I think Gandalf himself is totally bored of immortality
and just tries random fun shit to see what happens
and no one dares to argue with a man that can kick them before they reach him
the gang sets out, walks for ten minutes
before trolls capture and start to barbecue them
Gandalf, being an eternal being, has had time to work on his imitation skills
and they are so good they kill the troll
ten more minutes and they meet Elron
and hes like "This will all be retconned, so goodbye."
after sneaking away from goblins, Bilbo gets lost and finds a ring that can turn you invisible
probably not important so ignore it
then he challenges a creature named Gollum in riddles and cheats
which I didn't know you could do
the gang meets up again and Gandalf fucks off
because he's bored of this prank and now hes off to get an eagle drunk or something
then just chapters of "Were dwarves and were in danger. Help us babysitter!"
they find it
after a very short time
or long time depending on format
reach the dragon
"Hi Smog"
"Hi Bilbo, I have a weak spot near my heart"
"OK"
"Gonna go burn down Lake Town now"